Okay, so if these values do stick around
for a while, it is helpful to know how
to remove them when you want to target
them and specifically intentionally
remove them. So to do that, um you will
go ahead and access the storage location
that you're trying to access. So in our
case, local storage and then we can say
remove item. And here I can remove the
number item from local storage. So when
I hit enter, if I come over here to
application um and I go to local
storage, you can see I still have second
num and I have hello but I no longer
have the value uh or sorry I no longer
have the number key. If I want to remove
the hello key, I would say local storage
dot remove item and I would remove
hello.
Now, if I hit enter and I come back over
to my application, you can see that the
hello key is gone and we're not storing
that information anymore. The same works
for session storage. So, if I say
session storage remove item, I can go in
and find the hello item and remove it
just to show you that it's still there
right now as I haven't run it. It's
hello and it's storing my new value.
Now, when I run this remove item
and I go look at my application, you can
see it's gone. And that is how you
remove items from local insession